作为一个应用开发者
As an app developer,
有时候会忘记构建应用程序只是做了一半
you may sometimes forget that building the app is only half
而已
of the battle.
另一半则是推广安装
The other half is driving installs
以及确保用户继续回来使用
and making sure your users keep coming back.
但是  我们该如何做呢
But how do we go about doing this?
可以设计和实现用户参与和用户增长吗
Can engagement and user growth be designed and implemented
就像应用程序的任何其他组件那样
much like any other component of your application?
答案是肯定的  可以使用Google的技术
The answer is yes it can with the technology Google
来增强自己的应用程序
uses to power its own apps.
举个例子
Let's look at an example.
几年前  我和我的妻子去西班牙度假
A few years ago, my wife and I went for a vacation to Spain.
我们度过了一段美好的时光  但我记得最清楚的是
We had a wonderful time, but what I remember most vividly
我们在马拉加吃的一次美味的海鲜饭
is an amazing paella we had in the city of Malaga.
所以今天  如果Google能够帮我
So today, I would love it if Google could help me
做一份像那次那样的海鲜饭  我会非常乐意
cook a paella just like that.
现在假设你是开发者
Now suppose you, the developer, build
构建了一个应用程序
an app that, in fact, contains the recipe
它包含了一份地道的马拉加海鲜饭的食谱
for an authentic Malaga paella.
当我在Google上搜索时
When I'm searching on Google, your app
你的应用是展现为搜索结果中的一个
is presented as one of the search results
那么我可以立刻安装它
so I can install it right away.
或者  如果我已经安装过这个应用
Or, if I already have the app installed,
Google Search使用深层链接在你的应用中
Google Search takes me directly to the recipe in your app
直接打开这份食谱
using a deep link.
对的  就是这样
That's right.
有了应用程序索引  Google可以帮助
With app indexing, Google can help
用户发现应用程序里面的内容
users discover content inside of your app
并直接进入到应用中
and bring users wanting to make that tasty
让用户想要做出美味的海鲜饭
paella direct into your app.
找到食谱后  是时候让食谱应用
After finding the recipe, it is time for the recipe app
带我一步步走下去了
to walk me through the steps.
由于做海鲜饭  我的双手被占用了
Since my hands are occupied making the paella,
我可以说  OK  Google  并使用语音操作
I can say, OK, Google, and use voice actions
将食谱调出来
to invoke the recipe up.
通过语音操作  可以利用
With voice actions, you can take the advantage
Google语音识别功能和自然语言理解技术
of Google's speech recognition and natural language
无需编写大量的代码
understanding technology without having to write a ton of code.
你从我们的烹饪例子中看到
As you saw from our cooking example,
通过使用应用程序索引和语音操作
you can go beyond traditional web search
可以超越传统的网页搜索
by using app indexing and voice actions
为你的应用程序提供新的参与机会
to provide new engagement opportunities for your app
和新的用户体验
and offering new experiences for your users.
无论你是正在构建的应用是关于烹饪  旅游
Whether you are building an app for cooking, travel,
或任何其他很酷的新的使用案例  请按照以下两个步骤
or any other cool new use case, follow these two steps
来与Google Search进行整合
to integrate with Google Search.
首先  设置深层链接  使Google
First, set up your deep links so that the Google
机器人可以像抓取网站一样抓取它们
bot can crawl them much like it crawls websites.
什么是深层链接呢
What are deep links?
想像它们是在你的移动应用程序中作为
Think about them as a way to identify
识别一段特定的内容或功能的
a specific piece of content or functionality inside
一种方式
of your mobile application.
就像是网页中的网址一样  不过是针对应用程序的
Much like web URLs, but for apps.
当你的应用程序支持了深层链接
When your app supports deep linking,
你就可以通过使用应用程序索引进入Google的索引
you can get into the Google index by using app indexing.
一旦你的应用程序存在Google的索引中
Once your app is in the Google index,
第二步就是标注你的应用程序
the second step is to annotate your app
来描述它能做什么
to describe what it can do.
例如  你可以整合Google语音操作
For example, you can integrate Google Voice actions
以暴露应用程序的功能  用户可以使用语音进行激活
to expose app capabilities that users can activate with Voice.
使用应用索引API让Google理解你的应用程序的用法
Let Google understand your apps usage with app indexing API
通过自动完成功能
to enable re-engagement from the Google app
可以从Google应用重新接入
through auto completion.
最终  对于一些诸如旅游和娱乐的使用案例
Finally, for some use cases such as travel and entertainment,
你的电子邮件提醒可以以Google Now卡片的形式出现
your email reminder can appear as a Google Now card providing
提供给用户丰富的信息
the user with rich information that takes them back
使得他们返回到你的电子邮件  这里可以回到你的网站
to your email where they can return to your site.
通过与Google Search的整合
By integrating with Google Search,
你可以增加应用程序的安装
you can increase app installs, drive engagement
在Google Search的结果中通过深层链接驱动用户参与
through deep links in Google Search results,
并吸引用户使用语音操作这种很酷的新途径
and engage users in cool new ways with Voice actions.
如果你喜欢这个海鲜饭的故事
If you enjoyed the paella story, may I
我可以推荐一些伟大的示例代码作为甜点吗
recommend some great sample code for dessert?
请到developers.google.com/search来开始吧
To get started, go to developers.google.com/search.